dpauls.com 2019-03-08

# Privacy Policy of DPauls Travel & Tour

##### **Privacy Statement**

Thank you for visiting this web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Note:** The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. If you link to other web sites by clicking external links of third parties that may be found on our site, please review the privacy policies posted on those sites.

This statement describes and explains how we may collect and use information pertaining yourself through our website. Should you have any questions on our privacy policies, please click here to send an email to us. We understand and respect the importance of your privacy. The only way we will get any kind of personal information is if you give it to us when we specifically ask for it. We ask you for personal information in a variety of circumstances such as:

1\. When you make a reservation or purchase something from our website or through our customer service team - by email, letter, fax, or on the phone.

2\. When you register with us for promotions.

3\. When you take part in surveys or provide us with feedback.

All data we collect about you will be held under Indian law. When you provide information through the site you will be providing it to us as a whole, and should be aware that it may be accessed from countries whose laws provide various levels of protection for personal data, not always equivalent to the level of protection that may be provided in your own country. We use your Internet Protocol [IP] address to help diagnose problems with our server and/or to administer our Web site. We will not pass on any information about you to any third parties. We will restrict access to any Confidential Information provided by you to our employees, consultants, representatives, advisors and agents who need to know such information for the purposes of approving, evaluating or otherwise participating in the process of providing services and ensure that such employees, consultants, representatives, advisors and agents are fully aware of and agree to be bound by the terms of this statement in writing, prior to disclosure of such information to them. Anyone who is on either our mailing or e-mailing lists may elect at any time not to receive any future promotional information from us, or to have their details suppressed from our mailing lists.

##### **Cookie/Tracking Technology**

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.

**DPauls.com & its representatives can Call, SMS & Email with reference to your Travel enquiry. This consent will override any registration for DNC / NDNC. **

##### **Security**

This website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and/or alteration of information under our control. The data resides behind a firewall, with access restricted to our authorized personnel. All financial transactions are secured using 128 bit encryption, which is currently the strongest available for commercial use. In case your browser supports a lower level of encryption we suggest you upgrade your browser. Should you wish to address any questions pertaining to the security features of the website, please email to us.

##### **Privacy Contact Information**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: 

**By Email:** info@dpauls.com

**By Phone:** +91 9211787134

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted here.
